export default function() {
	return [
		{
	    answer: "Emmitt Smith",
	    question: "Who is the NFL's all-time leader in rushing yards?",
	    option_1: "Jim Brown",
	    option_2: "Barry Sanders",
	    option_3: "Emmitt Smith",
	    option_4: "Marshal Faulk",
	    id: "1"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Jerry Rice",
	    question: "Who is the NFL's all-time leader in receiving yards?",
	    option_1: "Chris Carter",
	    option_2: "Jerry Rice",
	    option_3: "Randy Moss",
	    option_4: "Art Monk",
	    id: "2"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "714",
	    question: "How many Home Runs did Babe Ruth hit in his career?",
	    option_1: "712",
	    option_2: "714",
	    option_3: "724",
	    option_4: "755",
	    id: "3"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "130",
	    question: "Most Stolen Bases that Rickey Henderson ever recorded in 1 season?",
	    option_1: "110",
	    option_2: "120",
	    option_3: "130",
	    option_4: "140",
	    id: "4"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "16",
	    question: "How many Gold Gloves did Brooks Robinson win during his career?",
	    option_1: "10",
	    option_2: "12",
	    option_3: "14",
	    option_4: "16",
	    id: "5"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
	    question: "Who's the NBA's all-time leading scorer?",
	    option_1: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
	    option_2: "Karl Malone",
	    option_3: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    option_4: "Michael Jordan",
	    id: "6"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    question: "Who's the NBA's all-time leading rebounder?",
	    option_1: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
	    option_2: "Tim Duncan",
	    option_3: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    option_4: "Bill Russell",
	    id: "7"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Michigan",
	    question: "What school leads NCAA football in all-time wins?",
	    option_1: "Michigan",
	    option_2: "Alabama",
	    option_3: "Texas",
	    option_4: "Ohio State",
	    id: "8"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Archie Griffin",
	    question: "Only 2 time Heisman Trophy winner?",
	    option_1: "Bo Jackson",
	    option_2: "Tim Tebow",
	    option_3: "OJ Simpson",
	    option_4: "Archie Griffin",
	    id: "9"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Eric Dickerson",
	    question: "Who set the NFL single season rushing record with 2,105 yards?",
	    option_1: "Adrian Peterson",
	    option_2: "OJ Simpson",
	    option_3: "Barry Sanders",
	    option_4: "Eric Dickerson",
	    id: "10"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "73",
	    question: "Most Home Runs hit in a single season?",
	    option_1: "68",
	    option_2: "70",
	    option_3: "73",
	    option_4: "75",
	    id: "11"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Chargers",
	    question: "What team was Eli Manning drafted by?",
	    option_1: "Chargers",
	    option_2: "Giants",
	    option_3: "Falcons",
	    option_4: "Colts",
	    id: "12"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "7",
	    question: "Most stolen bases by a player in a single game?",
	    option_1: "5",
	    option_2: "6",
	    option_3: "7",
	    option_4: "8",
	    id: "13"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "8",
	    question: "How many teams were in the first NCAA Basketball Tournament in 1939?",
	    option_1: "8",
	    option_2: "16",
	    option_3: "32",
	    option_4: "64",
	    id: "14"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "3rd",
	    question: "What pick number was Michael Jordan in the 1984 NBA Draft?",
	    option_1: "1st",
	    option_2: "2nd",
	    option_3: "3rd",
	    option_4: "4th",
	    id: "15"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    question: "Who holds the record for most points scored in an NBA game with 100?",
	    option_1: "Kobe Bryant",
	    option_2: "Michael Jordan",
	    option_3: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    option_4: "Pete Maravich",
	    id: "16"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "10",
	    question: "How many NCAA championships did John Wooden win as UCLA's basketball coach?",
	    option_1: "6",
	    option_2: "8",
	    option_3: "10",
	    option_4: "12",
	    id: "17"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Don Shula",
	    question: "Who's the NFL's all-time winningest coach with 328?",
	    option_1: "Bill Belichick",
	    option_2: "Vince Lombardi",
	    option_3: "Bill Walsh",
	    option_4: "Don Shula",
	    id: "18"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Packers",
	    question: "Which team won the first 2 Super Bowls?",
	    option_1: "Steelers",
	    option_2: "Packers",
	    option_3: "Cowboys",
	    option_4: "Colts",
	    id: "19"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Pete Maravich",
	    question: "Career scoring leader in NCAA basketball history with 3,367 points?",
	    option_1: "Larry Bird",
	    option_2: "Oscar Robertson",
	    option_3: "JJ Redick",
	    option_4: "Pete Maravich",
	    id: "20"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Dolphins",
	    question: "What NFL team was Nick Saban the head coach of?",
	    option_1: "Falcons",
	    option_2: "Colts",
	    option_3: "Dolphins",
	    option_4: "Browns",
	    id: "21"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Lou Brock",
	    question: "Who's record did Rickey Henderson break when he became the all-time stolen bases leader?",
	    option_1: "Ty Cobb",
	    option_2: "Lou Brock",
	    option_3: "Billy Hamilton",
	    option_4: "Honus Wagner",
	    id: "22"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Marcus Allen",
	    question: "This USC running back won the 1981 Heisman Trophy?",
	    option_1: "OJ Simpson",
	    option_2: "Marcus Allen",
	    option_3: "Charles White",
	    option_4: "Mike Garrett",
	    id: "23"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Mike Garrett",
	    question: "This USC running back won the 1965 Heisman Trophy?",
	    option_1: "OJ Simpson",
	    option_2: "Marcus Allen",
	    option_3: "Charles White",
	    option_4: "Mike Garrett",
	    id: "24"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "OJ Simpson",
	    question: "This USC running back won the 1968 Heisman Trophy?",
	    option_1: "OJ Simpson",
	    option_2: "Marcus Allen",
	    option_3: "Charles White",
	    option_4: "Mike Garrett",
	    id: "25"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Charles White",
	    question: "This USC running back won the 1979 Heisman Trophy?",
	    option_1: "OJ Simpson",
	    option_2: "Marcus Allen",
	    option_3: "Charles White",
	    option_4: "Mike Garrett",
	    id: "26"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Bo Jackson, AUB",
	    question: "This SEC running back won the 1985 Heisman Trophy?",
	    option_1: "Hershel Walker, UGA",
	    option_2: "Bo Jackson, AUB",
	    option_3: "Marcus Allen, USC",
	    option_4: "Barry Sanders, OSU",
	    id: "27"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
	    question: "This player has the most NBA MVP awards with 6?",
	    option_1: "Michael Jordan",
	    option_2: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    option_3: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
	    option_4: "Bill Russell",
	    id: "28"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Karl Malone",
	    question: "This player won 2 NBA MVP awards during the 90's?",
	    option_1: "Karl Malone",
	    option_2: "Michael Jordan",
	    option_3: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
	    option_4: "Charles Barkley",
	    id: "29"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Bill Russell",
	    question: "This NBA player has more championship rings (11), than fingers?",
	    option_1: "Wilt Chamberlain",
	    option_2: "Michael Jordan",
	    option_3: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
	    option_4: "Bill Russell",
	    id: "30"
	  },
	   {
	    answer: "3",
	    question: "The Lakers and Celtics met how many times in the NBA Finals during the 80's?",
	    option_1: "2",
	    option_2: "3",
	    option_3: "4",
	    option_4: "5",
	    id: "31"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "5",
	    question: "How many NBA MVP awards does Michael Jordan own?",
	    option_1: "3",
	    option_2: "4",
	    option_3: "5",
	    option_4: "6",
	    id: "32"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Marlins",
	    question: "Who beat the Indians to win the 1997 World Series?",
	    option_1: "Marlins",
	    option_2: "Diamondbacks",
	    option_3: "Braves",
	    option_4: "Giants",
	    id: "33"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "1989",
	    question: "What year was the battle of the bay World Series between the A's and Giants?",
	    option_1: "1988",
	    option_2: "1989",
	    option_3: "1990",
	    option_4: "1991",
	    id: "34"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "1994",
	    question: "There was no World Series this year due to the player's strike?",
	    option_1: "1991",
	    option_2: "1992",
	    option_3: "1993",
	    option_4: "1994",
	    id: "35"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Angels",
	    question: "This team beat the Giants in 7 games to win the 2002 World Series?",
	    option_1: "Angels",
	    option_2: "Yankees",
	    option_3: "Red Sox",
	    option_4: "White Sox",
	    id: "36"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Phillies",
	    question: "This team beat the Rays in 5 games to win the 2008 World Series?",
	    option_1: "Phillies",
	    option_2: "Giants",
	    option_3: "Marlins",
	    option_4: "Cardinals",
	    id: "37"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "7",
	    question: "How many NL MVP awards did Barry Bonds win?",
	    option_1: "4",
	    option_2: "5",
	    option_3: "6",
	    option_4: "7",
	    id: "38"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "3",
	    question: "How many NL MVP awards did Albert Pujols win?",
	    option_1: "2",
	    option_2: "3",
	    option_3: "4",
	    option_4: "5",
	    id: "39"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Larry Walker",
	    question: "The first ever Rockies player to win an NL MVP?",
	    option_1: "Todd Helton",
	    option_2: "Larry Walker",
	    option_3: "Troy Tulowitzki",
	    option_4: "Nolan Arenado",
	    id: "40"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Maurice Jones-Drew",
	    question: "This RB led the NFL in rushing in 2011 with 1,606 yards?",
	    option_1: "Maurice Jones-Drew",
	    option_2: "Adrian Peterson",
	    option_3: "Chris Johnson",
	    option_4: "Arian Foster",
	    id: "41"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Jamal Lewis",
	    question: "This RB led the NFL in rushing in 2003 with 2,066 yards?",
	    option_1: "Ricky Williams",
	    option_2: "Priest Holmes",
	    option_3: "Jamal Lewis",
	    option_4: "Edgerrin James",
	    id: "42"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "LaDainian Tomilson",
	    question: "This RB led the NFL in rushing in back to back seasons 2006-2007?",
	    option_1: "Arian Foster",
	    option_2: "LaDainian Tomilson",
	    option_3: "Adrian Peterson",
	    option_4: "Shaun Alexander",
	    id: "43"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Julio Jones",
	    question: "This WR led the NFL in receiving yards in 2015 with 1,871 yards?",
	    option_1: "Odell Beckham",
	    option_2: "Calvin Johnson",
	    option_3: "Antonio Brown",
	    option_4: "Julio Jones",
	    id: "44"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Brandon Lloyd",
	    question: "This WR led the NFL in receiving yards in 2010 with 1,448 yards?",
	    option_1: "Brandon Lloyd",
	    option_2: "Calvin Johnson",
	    option_3: "Andre Johnson",
	    option_4: "Reggie Wayne",
	    id: "45"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Andre Johnson",
	    question: "This WR led the NFL in receiving yards in back to back seasons 2008-2009?",
	    option_1: "Steve Smith",
	    option_2: "Calvin Johnson",
	    option_3: "Andre Johnson",
	    option_4: "Reggie Wayne",
	    id: "46"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Ben Roethlisberger",
	    question: "This QB led the NFL in passing yards in 2014 with 4,952 yards?",
	    option_1: "Peyton Manning",
	    option_2: "Tom Brady",
	    option_3: "Drew Brees",
	    option_4: "Ben Roethlisberger",
	    id: "47"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Daunte Culpepper",
	    question: "This QB led the NFL in passing yards in 2004 with 4,717 yards?",
	    option_1: "Peyton Manning",
	    option_2: "Daunte Culpepper",
	    option_3: "Drew Brees",
	    option_4: "Tom Brady",
	    id: "48"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Dan Marino",
	    question: "The 1st QB in NFL history to pass for over 5,000 yards in a season (1984)?",
	    option_1: "Dan Fouts",
	    option_2: "Joe Montana",
	    option_3: "Dan Marino",
	    option_4: "Lynn Dickey",
	    id: "49"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Joe Namath",
	    question: "The 1st QB in NFL history to pass for over 4,000 yards in a season (1967)?",
	    option_1: "Joe Namath",
	    option_2: "Sonny Jurgensen",
	    option_3: "Johnny Unitas",
	    option_4: "John Brodie",
	    id: "50"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for career passing yards with 19,217?",
	    option_1: "Timmy Chang, HAW",
	    option_2: "David Klingler, HOU",
	    option_3: "Peyton Manning, TEN",
	    option_4: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    id: "51"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Kevin Smith, UCF",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for most rushes in a season with 450?",
	    option_1: "LaDainian Tomilson, TCU",
	    option_2: "Ricky Williams, TEX",
	    option_3: "Kevin Smith, UCF",
	    option_4: "Hershel Walker, UGA",
	    id: "52"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Ron Dayne, WIS",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for career rushing yards with 6,397?",
	    option_1: "LaDainian Tomilson, TCU",
	    option_2: "Ricky Williams, TEX",
	    option_3: "DeAngelo Williams, MEM",
	    option_4: "Ron Dayne, WIS",
	    id: "53"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Barry Sanders, OSU",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for most rushing yards in a season with 2,628?",
	    option_1: "LaDainian Tomilson, TCU",
	    option_2: "Archie Griffin, OSU",
	    option_3: "Barry Sanders, OSU",
	    option_4: "Ron Dayne, WIS",
	    id: "54"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Keenan Reynolds, NAVY",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for career rushing TDs with 88?",
	    option_1: "Keenan Reynolds, NAVY",
	    option_2: "Archie Griffin, OSU",
	    option_3: "Hershel Walker, UGA",
	    option_4: "Ron Dayne, WIS",
	    id: "55"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Barry Sanders, OSU",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for most rushing TDs in a season with 37?",
	    option_1: "Keenan Reynolds, NAVY",
	    option_2: "Archie Griffin, OSU",
	    option_3: "Barry Sanders, OSU",
	    option_4: "Bo Jackson, AUB",
	    id: "56"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "BJ Symons, TTU",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for most passing yards in a season with 5,833?",
	    option_1: "Connor Halliday, WSU",
	    option_2: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    option_3: "BJ Symons, TTU",
	    option_4: "Timmy Chang, HAW",
	    id: "57"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for career passing TDs with 155?",
	    option_1: "Connor Halliday, WSU",
	    option_2: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    option_3: "Graham Harrell, TTU",
	    option_4: "Timmy Chang, HAW",
	    id: "58"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Colt Brennan, HAW",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for most passing TDs in a season with 58?",
	    option_1: "Connor Halliday, WSU",
	    option_2: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    option_3: "Graham Harrell, TTU",
	    option_4: "Colt Brennan, HAW",
	    id: "59"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Rakeem Cato, MAR",
	    question: "Who holds the NCAA record for most consecutive games throwing a TD pass with 46?",
	    option_1: "Rakeem Cato, MAR",
	    option_2: "Case Keenum, HOU",
	    option_3: "Graham Harrell, TTU",
	    option_4: "Colt Brennan, HAW",
	    id: "60"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Steelers",
	    question: "This team defeated the Cowboys 21-17 to win Super Bowl 10?",
	    option_1: "Colts",
	    option_2: "Steelers",
	    option_3: "Broncos",
	    option_4: "Raiders",
	    id: "61"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Bears",
	    question: "This team defeated the Patriots 46-10 to win Super Bowl 20?",
	    option_1: "Redskins",
	    option_2: "Vikings",
	    option_3: "Bears",
	    option_4: "49ers",
	    id: "62"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Raiders",
	    question: "This team defeated the Eagles 46-10 to win Super Bowl 15?",
	    option_1: "Steelers",
	    option_2: "Raiders",
	    option_3: "Broncos",
	    option_4: "Colts",
	    id: "63"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Broncos",
	    question: "This team defeated the Panthers 24-10 to win Super Bowl 50?",
	    option_1: "Steelers",
	    option_2: "Raiders",
	    option_3: "Broncos",
	    option_4: "Colts",
	    id: "64"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Steelers",
	    question: "This team defeated the Cardinals 27-23 to win Super Bowl 43?",
	    option_1: "Steelers",
	    option_2: "Raiders",
	    option_3: "Broncos",
	    option_4: "Colts",
	    id: "65"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Saints",
	    question: "This team defeated the Colts 31-17 to win Super Bowl 44?",
	    option_1: "49ers",
	    option_2: "Seahawks",
	    option_3: "Broncos",
	    option_4: "Saints",
	    id: "66"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "18",
	    question: "In inches, how big is the diameter of a basketball hoop?",
	    option_1: "12",
	    option_2: "18",
	    option_3: "24",
	    option_4: "30",
	    id: "67"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Dodgers",
	    question: "Which was the only team to win two World Series in the 1980s?",
	    option_1: "Yankees",
	    option_2: "Dodgers",
	    option_3: "Athletics",
	    option_4: "Mets",
	    id: "68"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "0",
	    question: "How many home runs did Ty Cobb hit in the 3 World Series in which he played?",
	    option_1: "0",
	    option_2: "3",
	    option_3: "5",
	    option_4: "7",
	    id: "69"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Dodgers",
	    question: "After retiring as a player, with which team did Babe Ruth spend 1 year as a coach?",
	    option_1: "Yankees",
	    option_2: "Dodgers",
	    option_3: "Red Sox",
	    option_4: "Giants",
	    id: "70"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Slam Dunk",
	    question: "What was banned in the NBA from 1967 to 1976?",
	    option_1: "Steroids",
	    option_2: "Free Throws",
	    option_3: "3 Pointer",
	    option_4: "Slam Dunk",
	    id: "71"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "10",
	    question: "In feet, how high is a NBA basketball hoop?",
	    option_1: "8",
	    option_2: "9",
	    option_3: "10",
	    option_4: "11",
	    id: "72"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Baseball",
	    question: "Name the only major team sport in the USA with no game clock?",
	    option_1: "Basketball",
	    option_2: "Football",
	    option_3: "Baseball",
	    option_4: "Boxing",
	    id: "73"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "Steelers",
	    question: "Which NFL team won 3 Super Bowls during the 70's?",
	    option_1: "49ers",
	    option_2: "Steelers",
	    option_3: "Cowboys",
	    option_4: "Packers",
	    id: "74"
	  },
	  {
	    answer: "49ers",
	    question: "Which NFL team won 3 Super Bowls during the 80's?",
	    option_1: "49ers",
	    option_2: "Steelers",
	    option_3: "Cowboys",
	    option_4: "Giants",
	    id: "75"
	  }
	];
}